<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>CVPR2020</title>
  <link>https://www.w3schools.com</link>
  <description>Free web building tutorials</description>
  <item>
    <title>Dual Super-Resolution Learning for Semantic Segmentation</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Wang_Dual_Super-Resolution_Learning_for_Semantic_Segmentation_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Current state-of-the-art semantic segmentation methods often apply high-resolution input to attain high performance, which brings large computation budgets and limits their applications on resource-constrained devices. In this paper, we propose a simple and flexible two-stream framework named Dual Super-Resolution Learning (DSRL) to effectively improve the segmentation accuracy without introducing extra computation costs. Specifically, the proposed method consists of three parts: Semantic Segmentation Super-Resolution (SSSR), Single Image Super-Resolution (SISR) and Feature Affinity (FA) module, which can keep high-resolution representations with low-resolution input while simultaneously reducing the model computation complexity. Moreover, it can be easily generalized to other tasks, e.g., human pose estimation. This simple yet effective method leads to strong representations and is evidenced by promising performance on both semantic segmentation and human pose estimation. Specifically, for semantic segmentation on CityScapes, we can achieve \geq2% higher mIoU with similar FLOPs, and keep the performance with 70% FLOPs. For human pose estimation, we can gain \geq2% mAP with the same FLOPs and maintain mAP with 30% fewer FLOPs. Code and models are available at https://github.com/wanglixilinx/DSRL.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Deep Unfolding Network for Image Super-Resolution</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Zhang_Deep_Unfolding_Network_for_Image_Super-Resolution_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Learning-based single image super-resolution (SISR) methods are continuously showing superior effectiveness and efficiency over traditional model-based methods, largely due to the end-to-end training. However, different from model-based methods that can handle the SISR problem with different scale factors, blur kernels and noise levels under a unified MAP (maximum a posteriori) framework, learning-based methods generally lack such flexibility. To address this issue, this paper proposes an end-to-end trainable unfolding network which leverages both learningbased methods and model-based methods. Specifically, by unfolding the MAP inference via a half-quadratic splitting algorithm, a fixed number of iterations consisting of alternately solving a data subproblem and a prior subproblem can be obtained. The two subproblems then can be solved with neural modules, resulting in an end-to-end trainable, iterative network. As a result, the proposed network inherits the flexibility of model-based methods to super-resolve blurry, noisy images for different scale factors via a single model, while maintaining the advantages of learning-based methods. Extensive experiments demonstrate the superiority of the proposed deep unfolding network in terms of flexibility, effectiveness and also generalizability.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Unsupervised Learning for Intrinsic Image Decomposition From a Single Image</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Liu_Unsupervised_Learning_for_Intrinsic_Image_Decomposition_From_a_Single_Image_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Intrinsic image decomposition, which is an essential task in computer vision, aims to infer the reflectance and shading of the scene. It is challenging since it needs to separate one image into two components. To tackle this, conventional methods introduce various priors to constrain the solution, yet with limited performance. Meanwhile, the problem is typically solved by supervised learning methods, which is actually not an ideal solution since obtaining ground truth reflectance and shading for massive general natural scenes is challenging and even impossible. In this paper, we propose a novel unsupervised intrinsic image decomposition framework, which relies on neither labeled training data nor hand-crafted priors. Instead, it directly learns the latent feature of reflectance and shading from unsupervised and uncorrelated data. To enable this, we explore the independence between reflectance and shading, the domain invariant content constraint and the physical constraint. Extensive experiments on both synthetic and real image datasets demonstrate consistently superior performance of the proposed method.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>COCAS: A Large-Scale Clothes Changing Person Dataset for Re-Identification</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Yu_COCAS_A_Large-Scale_Clothes_Changing_Person_Dataset_for_Re-Identification_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Recent years have witnessed great progress in person re-identification (re-id). Several academic benchmarks such as Market1501, CUHK03 and DukeMTMC play important roles to promote the re-id research. To our best knowledge, all the existing benchmarks assume the same person will have the same clothes. While in real-world scenarios, it is very often for a person to change clothes. To address the clothes changing person re-id problem, we construct a novel large-scale re-id benchmark named Clothes Changing Person Set (COCAS), which provides multiple images of the same identity with different clothes. COCAS totally contains 62,382 body images from 5,266 persons. Based on COCAS, we introduce a new person re-id setting for clothes changing problem, where the query includes both a clothes template and a person image taking another clothes. Moreover, we propose a two-branch network named Biometric-Clothes Network (BC-Net) which can effectively integrate biometric and clothes feature for re-id under our setting. Experiments show that it is feasible for clothes changing re-id with clothes templates.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Dynamic Convolutions: Exploiting Spatial Sparsity for Faster Inference</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Verelst_Dynamic_Convolutions_Exploiting_Spatial_Sparsity_for_Faster_Inference_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Modern convolutional neural networks apply the same operations on every pixel in an image. However, not all image regions are equally important. To address this inefficiency, we propose a method to dynamically apply convolutions conditioned on the input image. We introduce a residual block where a small gating branch learns which spatial positions should be evaluated. These discrete gating decisions are trained end-to-end using the Gumbel-Softmax trick, in combination with a sparsity criterion. Our experiments on CIFAR, ImageNet, Food-101 and MPII show that our method has better focus on the region of interest and better accuracy than existing methods, at a lower computational complexity. Moreover, we provide an efficient CUDA implementation of our dynamic convolutions using a gather-scatter approach, achieving a significant improvement in inference speed on MobileNetV2 and ShuffleNetV2. On human pose estimation, a task that is inherently spatially sparse, the processing speed is increased by 60% with no loss in accuracy.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Alleviation of Gradient Exploding in GANs: Fake Can Be Real</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Tao_Alleviation_of_Gradient_Exploding_in_GANs_Fake_Can_Be_Real_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>In order to alleviate the notorious mode collapse phenomenon in generative adversarial networks (GANs), we propose a novel training method of GANs in which certain fake samples are considered as real ones during the training process. This strategy can reduce the gradient value that generator receives in the region where gradient exploding happens. We show the process of an unbalanced generation and a vicious circle issue resulted from gradient exploding in practical training, which explains the instability of GANs. We also theoretically prove that gradient exploding can be alleviated by penalizing the difference between discriminator outputs and fake-as-real consideration for very close real and fake samples. Accordingly, Fake-As-Real GAN (FARGAN) is proposed with a more stable training process and a more faithful generated distribution. Experiments on different datasets verify our theoretical analysis.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Forward and Backward Information Retention for Accurate Binary Neural Networks</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Qin_Forward_and_Backward_Information_Retention_for_Accurate_Binary_Neural_Networks_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Weight and activation binarization is an effective approach to deep neural network compression and can accelerate the inference by leveraging bitwise operations. Although many binarization methods have improved the accuracy of the model by minimizing the quantization error in forward propagation, there remains a noticeable performance gap between the binarized model and the full-precision one. Our empirical study indicates that the quantization brings information loss in both forward and backward propagation, which is the bottleneck of training accurate binary neural networks. To address these issues, we propose an Information Retention Network (IR-Net) to retain the information that consists in the forward activations and backward gradients. IR-Net mainly relies on two technical contributions: (1) Libra Parameter Binarization (Libra-PB): simultaneously minimizing both quantization error and information loss of parameters by balanced and standardized weights in forward propagation; (2) Error Decay Estimator (EDE): minimizing the information loss of gradients by gradually approximating the sign function in backward propagation, jointly considering the updating ability and accurate gradients. We are the first to investigate both forward and backward processes of binary networks from the unified information perspective, which provides new insight into the mechanism of network binarization. Comprehensive experiments with various network structures on CIFAR-10 and ImageNet datasets manifest that the proposed IR-Net can consistently outperform state-of-the-art quantization methods.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cooling-Shrinking Attack: Blinding the Tracker With Imperceptible Noises</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Yan_Cooling-Shrinking_Attack_Blinding_the_Tracker_With_Imperceptible_Noises_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>Adversarial attack of CNN aims at deceiving models to misbehave by adding imperceptible perturbations to images. This feature facilitates to understand neural networks deeply and to improve the robustness of deep learning models. Although several works have focused on attacking image classifiers and object detectors, an effective and efficient method for attacking single object trackers of any target in a model-free way remains lacking. In this paper, a cooling-shrinking attack method is proposed to deceive state-of-the-art SiameseRPN-based trackers. An effective and efficient perturbation generator is trained with a carefully designed adversarial loss, which can simultaneously cool hot regions where the target exists on the heatmaps and force the predicted bounding box to shrink, making the tracked target invisible to trackers. Numerous experiments on OTB100, VOT2018, and LaSOT datasets show that our method can effectively fool the state-of-the-art SiameseRPN++ tracker by adding small perturbations to the template or the search regions. Besides, our method has good transferability and is able to deceive other top-performance trackers such as DaSiamRPN, DaSiamRPN-UpdateNet, and DiMP. The source codes are available at https://github.com/MasterBin-IIAU/CSA.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Zooming Slow-Mo: Fast and Accurate One-Stage Space-Time Video Super-Resolution</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Xiang_Zooming_Slow-Mo_Fast_and_Accurate_One-Stage_Space-Time_Video_Super-Resolution_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>In this paper, we explore the space-time video super-resolution task, which aims to generate a high-resolution (HR) slow-motion video from a low frame rate (LFR), low-resolution (LR) video. A simple solution is to split it into two sub-tasks: video frame interpolation (VFI) and video super-resolution (VSR). However, temporal interpolation and spatial super-resolution are intra-related in this task. Two-stage methods cannot fully take advantage of the natural property. In addition, state-of-the-art VFI or VSR networks require a large frame-synthesis or reconstruction module for predicting high-quality video frames, which makes the two-stage methods have large model sizes and thus be time-consuming. To overcome the problems, we propose a one-stage space-time video super-resolution framework, which directly synthesizes an HR slow-motion video from an LFR, LR video. Rather than synthesizing missing LR video frames as VFI networks do, we firstly temporally interpolate LR frame features in missing LR video frames capturing local temporal contexts by the proposed feature temporal interpolation network. Then, we propose a deformable ConvLSTM to align and aggregate temporal information simultaneously for better leveraging global temporal contexts. Finally, a deep reconstruction network is adopted to predict HR slow-motion video frames. Extensive experiments on benchmark datasets demonstrate that the proposed method not only achieves better quantitative and qualitative performance but also is more than three times faster than recent two-stage state-of-the-art methods, e.g., DAIN+EDVR and DAIN+RBPN.</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A Hierarchical Graph Network for 3D Object Detection on Point Clouds</title>
    <link>https://openaccess.thecvf.com/content_CVPR_2020/papers/Chen_A_Hierarchical_Graph_Network_for_3D_Object_Detection_on_Point_CVPR_2020_paper.pdf</link>
    <description>3D object detection on point clouds finds many applications. However, most known point cloud object detection methods did not adequately accommodate the characteristics (e.g., sparsity) of point clouds, and thus some key semantic information (e.g., shape information) is not well captured. In this paper, we propose a new graph convolution (GConv) based hierarchical graph network (HGNet) for 3D object detection, which processes raw point clouds directly to predict 3D bounding boxes. HGNet effectively captures the relationship of the points and utilizes the multi-level semantics for object detection. Specially, we propose a novel shape-attentive GConv (SA-GConv) to capture the local shape features, by modelling the relative geometric positions of points to describe object shapes. An SA-GConv based U-shape network captures the multi-level features, which are mapped into an identical feature space by an improved voting module and then further utilized to generate proposals. Next, a new GConv based Proposal Reasoning Module reasons on the proposals considering the global scene semantics, and the bounding boxes are then predicted. Consequently, our new framework outperforms state-of-the-art methods on two large-scale point cloud datasets, by  4% mean average precision (mAP) on SUN RGB-D and by  3% mAP on ScanNet-V2.</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>
